Guide to the Graduate School of Arts and Sciences, Yale University, Student Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Student grade lists, circa 1932-1975; Accession 2005-A-048
  - French -A Term, 1970-1971 (Box 11, Folder 596)
  - French -B Term, 1970-1971 (Box 11, Folder 597)
  - Geology -1970-1971 (Box 12, Folder 598)
  - German -A Term, 1970-1971 (Box 12, Folder 599)
  - German -B Term, 1970-1971 (Box 12, Folder 600)
  - German -Full Year, 1970-1971 (Box 12, Folder 601)
  - History -A Term, 1970-1971 (Box 12, Folder 602)
  - History -B Term, 1970-1971 (Box 12, Folder 603)
  - History -Full Year, 1970-1971 (Box 12, Folder 604)
  - History of Art -A Term, 1970-1971 (Box 12, Folder 605)
  - History of Art -B Term, 1970-1971 (Box 12, Folder 606)
  - History of Art -Full Year, 1970-1971 (Box 12, Folder 607)
  - History of Science and Medicine -1970-1971 (Box 12, Folder 608)
  - Music -A Term, 1970-1971 (Box 12, Folder 609)
  - Music -B Term, 1970-1971 (Box 12, Folder 610)
  - Music -Full Year, 1970-1971 (Box 12, Folder 611)
  - Italian -A Term, 1970-1971 (Box 12, Folder 612)
  - Italian -B Term, 1970-1971 (Box 12, Folder 613)
  - Linguistics -A Term, 1970-1971 (Box 12, Folder 614)
  - Linguistics -B Term, 1970-1971 (Box 12, Folder 615)
  - Mathematics -1970-1971 (Box 12, Folder 616)
  - Medieval Studies -1970-1971 (Box 12, Folder 617)
  - Microbiology -A Term, 1970-1971 (Box 12, Folder 618)
  - Microbiology -B Term, 1970-1971 (Box 12, Folder 619)
  - Molecular Biophysics and Biochemistry -A Term, 1970-1971 (Box 12, Folder 620)
  - Molecular Biophysics and Biochemistry -B Term, 1970-1971 (Box 12, Folder 621)
  - Near Eastern Languages and Literatures -A Term, 1970-1971 (Box 12, Folder 622)
  - Near Eastern Languages and Literatures -B Term, 1970-1971 (Box 12, Folder 623)
  - Pharmacology -A Term, 1970-1971 (Box 12, Folder 624)
  - Pharmacology -B Term, 1970-1971 (Box 12, Folder 625)
  - Physics -1970-1971 (Box 12, Folder 626)
  - Political Science -1970-1971 (Box 12, Folder 627)
  - Physiology -A Term, 1970-1971 (Box 12, Folder 628)
  - Physiology -B Term, 1970-1971 (Box 12, Folder 629)
  - Physiology -Full Year, 1970-1971 (Box 12, Folder 630)
  - Portuguese -A Term, 1970-1971 (Box 12, Folder 631)
  - Philosophy -A Term, 1970-1971 (Box 12, Folder 632)
  - Philosophy -B Term, 1970-1971 (Box 12, Folder 633)
  - Psychology -1970-1971 (Box 12, Folder 634)
  - Religious Studies -A Term, 1970-1971 (Box 12, Folder 635)
  - Religious Studies -B Term, 1970-1971 (Box 12, Folder 636)
  - Russian -A Term, 1970-1971 (Box 12, Folder 637)
  - Russian -B Term, 1970-1971 (Box 12, Folder 638)
  - Russian -Full Year, 1970-1971 (Box 12, Folder 639)
  - Sociology -A Term, 1970-1971 (Box 12, Folder 640)
  - Sociology -B Term, 1970-1971 (Box 12, Folder 641)
  - Spanish -A Term, 1970-1971 (Box 12, Folder 642)
  - Spanish -B Term, 1970-1971 (Box 12, Folder 643)
  - Statistics, 1970-1971 (Box 12, Folder 644)
  - Undergraduate, 1970-1971 (Box 12, Folder 645 - 647)
  - Other Schools, 1970-1971 (Box 12, Folder 648)
  - 1967-1968, Professor's Last Name Beginning with
    - A (Box 13, Folder 649)
    - B (Box 13, Folder 650)
    - C (Box 13, Folder 651)
    - D (Box 13, Folder 652)
    - E (Box 13, Folder 653)
    - F (Box 13, Folder 654)
    - G (Box 13, Folder 655)
    - H (Box 13, Folder 656)
    - I (Box 13, Folder 657)
    - J (Box 13, Folder 658)
    - K (Box 13, Folder 659)
    - L (Box 13, Folder 660)
    - M (Box 13, Folder 661)
    - Mc (Box 13, Folder 662)
    - N (Box 13, Folder 663)
    - O (Box 13, Folder 664)
    - P (Box 13, Folder 665)
    - Q (Box 13, Folder 666)
    - R (Box 13, Folder 667)
    - S (Box 14, Folder 668)
    - T (Box 14, Folder 669)
    - U (Box 14, Folder 670)
    - V (Box 14, Folder 671)
    - W (Box 14, Folder 672)
    - XYZ (Box 14, Folder 673)
  - 1966-1967, Professor's Last Name Beginning with
    - A (Box 14, Folder 674)
    - B (Box 14, Folder 675)
    - C (Box 14, Folder 676)
    - D (Box 14, Folder 677)
    - E (Box 14, Folder 678)
    - F (Box 14, Folder 679)
    - G (Box 14, Folder 680)
    - H (Box 14, Folder 681)
    - I (Box 14, Folder 682)
    - J (Box 14, Folder 683)
    - K (Box 14, Folder 684)
    - Grade Extensions (Box 14, Folder 685)
    - M (Box 15, Folder 686)
    - Mc (Box 15, Folder 687)
    - N (Box 15, Folder 688)
    - O (Box 15, Folder 689)
    - P (Box 15, Folder 690)
    - Q (Box 15, Folder 691)
    - R (Box 15, Folder 692)
    - S (Box 15, Folder 693)
    - T (Box 15, Folder 694)
    - U (Box 15, Folder 695)
    - W (Box 15, Folder 696)
  - 1966-1967, Professor's Last Name Beginning with K (Box 15, Folder 697 - 700)
  - Administrative Sciences, 1972-1973 (Box 15, Folder 701 - 703)
  - American Studies, 1972-1973 (Box 15, Folder 704 - 706)
  - Anatomy, 1972-1973 (Box 15, Folder 707 - 709)
  - Anthropology, 1972-1973 (Box 15, Folder 710 - 712)
  - Astronomy, 1972-1973 (Box 15, Folder 713 - 715)
  - Biology, 1972-1973 (Box 15, Folder 716 - 718)
  - Chemistry, 1972-1973 (Box 15, Folder 719 - 721)
  - 1965-1966, Professor's Last Name Beginning with
    - A (Box 16, Folder 722)
    - B (Box 16, Folder 723)
    - C (Box 16, Folder 724)
    - D (Box 16, Folder 725)
    - E (Box 16, Folder 726)
    - G (Box 16, Folder 727)
    - H (Box 16, Folder 728)
    - I (Box 16, Folder 729)
    - J (Box 16, Folder 730)
    - K (Box 16, Folder 731)
    - L (Box 16, Folder 732)
    - M (Box 16, Folder 733)
    - Mc (Box 16, Folder 734)
    - N (Box 16, Folder 735)
    - O (Box 16, Folder 736)
    - P (Box 16, Folder 737)
    - Q (Box 16, Folder 738)
    - R (Box 16, Folder 739)
    - S (Box 16, Folder 740)
    - T (Box 16, Folder 741)
    - U (Box 16, Folder 742)
    - V (Box 16, Folder 743)
    - W (Box 16, Folder 744)
    - XYZ (Box 16, Folder 745)
  - Grade Extensions, 1965-1966 (Box 16, Folder 746)
  - 1963-1964, Professor's Last Name Beginning with
    - A (Box 16, Folder 747)
    - B (Box 16, Folder 748)
    - C (Box 16, Folder 749)
    - D (Box 16, Folder 750)
    - E (Box 17, Folder 751)
    - F (Box 17, Folder 752)
    - G (Box 17, Folder 753)
    - H (Box 17, Folder 754)
    - I (Box 17, Folder 755)
    - J (Box 17, Folder 756)
    - K (Box 17, Folder 757)
    - L (Box 17, Folder 758)
    - M (Box 17, Folder 759)
    - N (Box 17, Folder 760)
    - O (Box 17, Folder 761)
    - P (Box 17, Folder 762)
    - Q (Box 17, Folder 763)
    - R (Box 17, Folder 764)
    - S (Box 17, Folder 765)
    - T (Box 17, Folder 766)
    - U (Box 17, Folder 767)
    - V (Box 17, Folder 768)
    - W (Box 17, Folder 769)
    - XYZ (Box 17, Folder 770)
  - 1963-1964 -Final Grades (Box 17, Folder 771)
  - 1932-1933, Professor's Last Name Beginning with
    - A-D (Box 17, Folder 772)
    - E-N (Box 17, Folder 773)
    - O-Z (Box 17, Folder 774)
  - 1933-1934, Professor's Last Name Beginning with
    - A-D (Box 17, Folder 775)
    - E-N (Box 17, Folder 776)
    - O-Z (Box 17, Folder 777)
  - 1934-1935, Professor's Last Name Beginning with
    - A-F (Box 18, Folder 778)
    - G-Q (Box 18, Folder 779)
    - R-Z (Box 18, Folder 780)
  - 1935-1936, Professor's Last Name Beginning with
    - A-F (Box 18, Folder 781)
    - G-Q (Box 18, Folder 782)
    - R-Z (Box 18, Folder 783)
  - 1936-1937, Professor's Last Name Beginning with
    - A-F (Box 18, Folder 784)
    - G-Q (Box 18, Folder 785)
    - R-Z (Box 18, Folder 786)
  - 1937-1938, Professor's Last Name Beginning with
    - A-F (Box 18, Folder 787)
    - G-Q (Box 18, Folder 788)
    - R-Z (Box 18, Folder 789)
  - 1938-1939, Professor's Last Name Beginning with
    - A-F (Box 18, Folder 790)
    - G-Q (Box 18, Folder 791)
    - R-Z (Box 18, Folder 792)
  - 1939-1940, Professor's Last Name Beginning with
    - A-F (Box 18, Folder 793)
    - G-Q (Box 18, Folder 794)
    - R-Z (Box 18, Folder 795)
  - 1940-1941, Professor's Last Name Beginning with
    - A-F (Box 19, Folder 796)
    - G-Q (Box 19, Folder 797)
    - R-Z (Box 19, Folder 798)
  - 1941-1942, Professor's Last Name Beginning with
    - A-F (Box 19, Folder 799)
    - G-Q (Box 19, Folder 800)
    - R-Z (Box 19, Folder 801)
  - 1942-1943, Professor's Last Name Beginning with
    - A-F (Box 19, Folder 802)
    - G-Q (Box 19, Folder 803)
    - R-Z (Box 19, Folder 804)
  - 1943-1944, Professor's Last Name Beginning with
    - A-F (Box 19, Folder 805)
    - G-Q (Box 19, Folder 806)
    - R-Z (Box 19, Folder 807)
  - 1944-1945, Professor's Last Name Beginning with
    - A-F (Box 19, Folder 808)
    - G-Q (Box 19, Folder 809)
    - R-Z (Box 19, Folder 810)
  - 1945-1946, Professor's Last Name Beginning with
    - A-F (Box 19, Folder 811)
    - G-Q (Box 19, Folder 812)
    - R-Z (Box 19, Folder 813)
  - 1946-1947, Professor's Last Name Beginning with
    - A-F (Box 19, Folder 814)
    - G-Q (Box 19, Folder 815)
    - R-Z (Box 20, Folder 816)
  - 1947-1948, Professor's Last Name Beginning with
    - A-F (Box 20, Folder 817)
    - G-Q (Box 20, Folder 818)
    - R-Z (Box 20, Folder 819)
  - 1954-1955, Professor's Last Name Beginning with
    - A-F (Box 20, Folder 820)
    - G-Q (Box 20, Folder 821)
    - R-Z (Box 20, Folder 822)
  - 1955-1956, Professor's Last Name Beginning with
    - A-F (Box 20, Folder 823)
    - G-Q (Box 20, Folder 824)
    - R-Z (Box 20, Folder 825)
  - 1957-1958, Professor's Last Name Beginning with
    - A-F (Box 20, Folder 826)
    - G-Q (Box 21, Folder 827)
    - R-Z (Box 21, Folder 828)
  - 1959-1960, Professor's Last Name Beginning with
    - A-C (Box 21, Folder 829)
    - D-K (Box 21, Folder 830)
    - L-R (Box 21, Folder 831)
    - S-Z (Box 21, Folder 832)
  - 1959-1960
    - Miscellaneous Departmental Grades (Box 21, Folder 833)
    - History of Art (Box 21, Folder 834)
  - 1960-1961, Professor's Last Name Beginning with
    - A-E (Box 21, Folder 835)
    - F-L (Box 21, Folder 836)
    - M-R (Box 22, Folder 837)
    - S-Z (Box 22, Folder 838)
  - 1960-1961, Miscellaneous Departmental Grades (Box 22, Folder 839)
  - 1961-1962, Miscellaneous Departmental Grades (Box 22, Folder 840)
  - 1961-1962, Professor's Last Name Beginning with
    - A-C (Box 22, Folder 841)
    - D-H (Box 22, Folder 842)
    - I-N (Box 22, Folder 843)
    - O-S (Box 22, Folder 844)
    - T-Z (Box 22, Folder 845)
- Student dossiers files, 1950-1998; Accession 2006-A-143
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2074
- Student transcripts, 1950-1989; Accession 2006-A-152
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2065
  - Miyashiro, Clifford Kiyoichi (Box 3, Folder 4001)
  - Ruttenberg, John C (Box 3, Folder 5001)
  - Weintraub, Mark Stephen (Box 4, Folder 6001)
- Student dossier files, 1965-1999; Accession 2007-A-138
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2075
- Graduate student dossier files, 1990-2007; Accession 2008-A-153
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2083
  - Scanned
  - Not scanned
- Student records and grades, 1970-2007; Accession 2016-A-046
  Restricted until January 1, 2082
  - Master's Degree Student Files
  - PhD Degree Student Files
  - GSAS Exchange Scholar Student Records
    - 1988-1989 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - 1989-1990 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - 1990-1991 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - 1991-1992 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - 1992-1993 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - 1993-1994 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - 1994-1995 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - 1995-1996 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - 1996-1997 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - 1997-1998 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - 1998-1999 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - 1999-2000 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - 2000-2001 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - 2001-2002 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - 2002-2003 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Spring 2003 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - 2003-2004 (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - 2004-2005 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - Fall 2004 (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - Spring 2005 (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - Fall 2005 (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - Fall 2006 (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - 2011-2012 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - GSAS Grades, 2003-2004, African Studies-Pharmacology
    - African Studies Grades Fall 2003, 2003-2004 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - African Studies Grades Spring 2004, 2003-2004 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - African-American Studies Fall 2003 Grades, 2003-2004 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - African-American Studies Spring 2004 Grades, 2003-2004 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Amercian Studies Fall 2003 Grades, 2003-2004 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - American Studies Spring 2004 Grades, 2003-2004 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Anthropology Fall 2003 Grades, 2003-2004 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Anthropology Spring 2004 Grades, 2003-2004 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Archeological Studies Fall 2003 Grades, 2003-2004 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Archeological Studies Spring 2004 Grades, 2003-2004 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Astronomy Fall 2003 Grades, 2003-2004 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Astronomy Spring 2004 Grades, 2003-2004 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Biology Spring 2004 Grades, 2003-2004 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Cell Biology Fall 2003 Grades, 2003-2004 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Cell Biology Spring 2004 Grades, 2003-2004 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Cellular Molecular Physiology Fall 2003 Grades, 2003-2004 (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Cellular Molecular Physiology Spring 2004 Grades, 2003-2004 (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Chemistry Fall 2003 Grades, 2003-2004 (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - Chemistry Spring 2004 Grades, 2003-2004 (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - Classics Fall 2003 Grades, 2003-2004 (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - Classics Spring 2004 Grades, 2003-2004 (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - Comparative Literature Fall 2003 Grades, 2003-2004 (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - Comparative Literature Spring 2004 Grades, 2003-2004 (Box 15, Folder 23)
    - Computer Science Fall 2003 Grades, 2003-2004 (Box 15, Folder 24)
    - Computer Science Spring 2004 Grades, 2003-2004 (Box 15, Folder 25)
    - East Asian Languages Lit Fall 2003 Grades, 2003-2004 (Box 15, Folder 26)
    - East Asian Languages Lit Spring 2004 Grades, 2003-2004 (Box 15, Folder 27)
    - East Asian Studies Fall 2003, 2003-2004 (Box 15, Folder 28)
    - East Asian Studies Spring 2004, 2003-2004 (Box 15, Folder 29)
    - Ecology Evolutionary Biology Fall 2003, 2003-2004 (Box 15, Folder 30)
    - Ecology Evolutionary Biology Spring 2004, 2003-2004 (Box 15, Folder 31)
    - Economics Fall 2003 Grades, 2003-2004 (Box 15, Folder 32)
    - Economics Spring 2004 Grades, 2003-2004 (Box 15, Folder 33)
    - Engineering Applied Science Fall 2003, 2003-2004 (Box 15, Folder 34)
    - Engineering Applied Science Spring 2004, 2003-2004 (Box 15, Folder 35)
    - English Languages Literature Fall 2003 Grades, 2003-2004 (Box 15, Folder 36)
    - English Languages Literature Spring 2004 Grades, 2003-2004 (Box 15, Folder 37)
    - Epidemiology Public Health Fall 2003 Grades, 2003-2004 (Box 15, Folder 38)
    - Epidemiology Public Health Spring 2004 Grades, 2003-2004 (Box 15, Folder 39)
    - Experimental Pathology Fall 2003 Grades, 2003-2004 (Box 15, Folder 40)
    - Experimental Pathology Spring 2004 Grades, 2003-2004 (Box 15, Folder 41)
    - Film Studies Fall 2003, 2003-2004 (Box 15, Folder 42)
    - Film Studies Spring 2004, 2003-2004 (Box 15, Folder 43)
    - Forestry Environmental Studies Fall 2003 Grades, 2003-2004 (Box 15, Folder 44)
    - Forestry Environmental Studies Spring 2004 Grades, 2003-2004 (Box 15, Folder 45)
    - French Fall 2003 Grades, 2003-2004 (Box 15, Folder 46)
    - French Spring 2004 Grades, 2003-2004 (Box 15, Folder 47)
    - Genetics Fall 2003 Grades, 2003-2004 (Box 15, Folder 48)
    - Genetics Spring 2004 Grades, 2003-2004 (Box 15, Folder 49)
    - Geology Geophysics Fall 2003 Grades, 2003-2004 (Box 15, Folder 50)
    - Geology Geophysics Spring 2004 Grades, 2003-2004 (Box 15, Folder 51)
    - Germanic Languages Literature Fall 2003 Grades, 2003-2004 (Box 15, Folder 52)
    - Germanic Languages Literature Spring 2004 Grades, 2003-2004 (Box 15, Folder 53)
    - History Fall 2003 Grades, 2003-2004 (Box 15, Folder 54)
    - History Spring 2004 Grades, 2003-2004 (Box 15, Folder 55)
    - History of Art Fall Grades 2003, 2003-2004 (Box 15, Folder 56)
    - History of Medicine Science Fall 2003 Grades, 2003-2004 (Box 15, Folder 58)
    - History of Medicine Science Spring 2004 Grades, 2003-2004 (Box 15, Folder 59)
    - Immunobiology Fall 2003 Grades, 2003-2004 (Box 15, Folder 60)
    - Immunobiology Spring 2004 Grades, 2003-2004 (Box 15, Folder 61)
    - International Relations Fall 2003 Grades, 2003-2004 (Box 15, Folder 62)
    - International Relations Spring 2004 Grades, 2003-2004 (Box 15, Folder 63)
    - Investigative Medicine Fall 2003, 2003-2004 (Box 15, Folder 64)
    - Investigative Medicine Spring 2004, 2003-2004 (Box 15, Folder 65)
    - Italian Fall 2003 Grades, 2003-2004 (Box 15, Folder 66)
    - Italian Spring 2004 Grades, 2003-2004 (Box 15, Folder 67)
    - Latin American Studies Spring 2004 Grades, 2003-2004 (Box 15, Folder 68)
    - Linguistics Fall 2003 Grades, 2003-2004 (Box 15, Folder 69)
    - Linguistics Spring 2004 Grades, 2003-2004 (Box 15, Folder 70)
    - Management Fall 2003 Grades, 2003-2004 (Box 15, Folder 71)
    - Management Spring 2004 Grades, 2003-2004 (Box 15, Folder 72)
    - Mathematics Fall 2003 Grades, 2003-2004 (Box 15, Folder 73)
    - Mathematics Spring 2004 Grades, 2003-2004 (Box 15, Folder 74)
    - MD/PhD Program Spring 2004 Grades, 2003-2004 (Box 15, Folder 75)
    - Medieval Spring 2004 Grades, 2003-2004 (Box 15, Folder 76)
    - Microbiology Fall 2003 Grades, 2003-2004 (Box 15, Folder 77)
    - Microbiology Spring 2004 Grades, 2003-2004 (Box 15, Folder 78)
    - Molecular Biophysics Biochem Fall 2003, 2003-2004 (Box 15, Folder 79)
    - Molecular Biophysics Biochem Spring 2004, 2003-2004 (Box 15, Folder 80)
    - Molecular, Cell Development Biology Fall 2003 Grades, 2003-2004 (Box 15, Folder 81)
    - Molecular, Cell Development Biology Spring 2004 Grades, 2003-2004 (Box 15, Folder 82)
    - Music Fall 2003 Grades, 2003-2004 (Box 15, Folder 83)
    - Music Spring 2004 Grades, 2003-2004 (Box 15, Folder 84)
    - Near Eastern Languages Civilization Fall 2003 Grades, 2003-2004 (Box 15, Folder 85)
    - Near Eastern Languages Civilization Spring 2004 Grades, 2003-2004 (Box 15, Folder 86)
    - Neurobiology Spring 2004 Grades, 2003-2004 (Box 15, Folder 87)
    - Neuroscience Fall 2003 Grades, 2003-2004 (Box 15, Folder 88)
    - Neuroscience Spring 2004 Grades, 2003-2004 (Box 15, Folder 89)
    - Pharmacology Fall 2003 Grades, 2003-2004 (Box 15, Folder 90)
    - Pharmacology Spring 2004 Grades, 2003-2004 (Box 15, Folder 91)
  - GSAS Grades, 2003-2004, Philosophy-end
    - Philosophy Fall 2003 Grades, 2003-2004 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Philosophy Spring 2004 Grades, 2003-2004 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Physics Fall 2003 Grades, 2003-2004 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Physics Spring 2004 Grades, 2003-2004 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Political Science Fall 2003 Grades, 2003-2004 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Political Science Spring 2004 Grades, 2003-2004 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Psychology Fall 2003 Grades, 2003-2004 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Psychology Spring 2004 Grades, 2003-2004 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Religious Studies Fall 2003 Grades, 2003-2004 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Religious Studies Spring 2004 Grades, 2003-2004 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Renaissance Studies Fall 2003, 2003-2004 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Renaissance Studies Fall 2004, 2003-2004 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Russian, East European Hellenic Studies Fall 2003 Grades, 2003-2004 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Russian, East European Hellenic Studies Fall 2004 Grades, 2003-2004 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Slavic Languages Lit Fall 2003 Grades, 2003-2004 (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Slavic Languages Lit Spring 2004 Grades, 2003-2004 (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Sociology Fall 2003 Grades, 2003-2004 (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - Sociology Spring 2004 Grades, 2003-2004 (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - Spanish Portuguese Fall 2003 Grades, 2003-2004 (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - Spanish Portuguese Spring Grades 2004, 2003-2004 (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - Statistics Fall 2003 Grades, 2003-2004 (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - Statistics Spring 2004 Grades, 2003-2004 (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - Teacher Prep Fall 2003, 2003-2004 (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - Teacher Prep Spring 2004, 2003-2004 (Box 16, Folder 24)
    - Women Gender Studies Fall 2003 Grades, 2003-2004 (Box 16, Folder 25)
    - Women Gender Studies Spring 2004 Grades, 2003-2004 (Box 16, Folder 26)
    - Architecture Grades Fall 2003, 2003-2004 (Box 16, Folder 27)
    - Law School Grades Fall 2003, 2003-2004 (Box 16, Folder 28)
    - Law School Grades Spring 2004, 2003-2004 (Box 16, Folder 29)
    - Divinity School Grades Fall 2003, 2003-2004 (Box 16, Folder 30)
    - Divinity School Grades Spring 2004, 2003-2004 (Box 16, Folder 31)
    - Drama Grades Spring 2004, 2003-2004 (Box 16, Folder 32)
    - Nursing Grades Fall 2003, 2003-2004 (Box 16, Folder 33)
    - Art Grades Fall 2003, 2003-2004 (Box 16, Folder 34)
    - Art Grades Spring 2004, 2003-2004 (Box 16, Folder 35)
    - Visiting Assistant In Research Grades Spring 2004, 2003-2004 (Box 16, Folder 36)
  - GSAS Grades, 2004-2005, Accounting-History of Art
    - Accounting Spring 2005, 2004-2005 (Box 16, Folder 37)
    - African Studies Fall 2004 Grades, 2004-2005 (Box 16, Folder 38)
    - African Studies Spring 2005 Grades, 2004-2005 (Box 16, Folder 39)
    - African-American Studies Fall 2004 Grades, 2004-2005 (Box 16, Folder 40)
    - African-American Studies Spring 2005 Grades, 2004-2005 (Box 16, Folder 41)
    - American Studies Fall 2004 Grades, 2004-2005 (Box 16, Folder 42)
    - American Studies Spring 2005 Grades, 2004-2005 (Box 16, Folder 43)
    - Anthropology Fall 2004 Grades, 2004-2005 (Box 16, Folder 44)
    - Anthropology 2005 Grades, 2004-2005 (Box 16, Folder 45)
    - Archaeology Fall 2004 Grades, 2004-2005 (Box 16, Folder 47)
    - Architecture Grades Fall 2004, 2004-2005 (Box 16, Folder 48)
    - Architecture Grades Spring 2005, 2004-2005 (Box 16, Folder 49)
    - Art Grades Fall 2004, 2004-2005 (Box 16, Folder 50)
    - Art Grades Spring 2005, 2004-2005 (Box 16, Folder 51)
    - Astronomy Fall 2004 Grades, 2004-2005 (Box 16, Folder 52)
    - Astronomy Spring 2005 Grades, 2004-2005 (Box 16, Folder 53)
    - Biology Grades Fall 2004, 2004-2005 (Box 16, Folder 54)
    - Cell Biology Fall 2004 Grades, 2004-2005 (Box 16, Folder 55)
    - Cell Biology Spring 2005 Grades, 2004-2005 (Box 16, Folder 56)
    - Cellular Molecular Physiology Fall 2004, 2004-2005 (Box 16, Folder 57)
    - Cellular Molecular Physiology Spring 2005, 2004-2005 (Box 16, Folder 58)
    - Chemistry Fall 2004 Grades, 2004-2005 (Box 16, Folder 59)
    - Chemistry Spring 2005 Grades, 2004-2005 (Box 16, Folder 60)
    - Classics Fall 2004 Grades, 2004-2005 (Box 16, Folder 61)
    - Classics Spring 2005 Grades, 2004-2005 (Box 16, Folder 62)
    - Comparative Literature Fall 2004 Grades, 2004-2005 (Box 16, Folder 63)
    - Comparative Literature Spring 2005 Grades, 2004-2005 (Box 16, Folder 64)
    - Computer Science Fall 2004 Grades, 2004-2005 (Box 16, Folder 65)
    - Computer Science Spring 2005 Grades, 2004-2005 (Box 16, Folder 66)
    - East Asian Languages Lit Fall 2004 Grades, 2004-2005 (Box 16, Folder 67)
    - East Asian Languages Lit Spring 2005 Grades, 2004-2005 (Box 16, Folder 68)
    - East Asian Studies Spring 2005 Grades, 2004-2005 (Box 16, Folder 68A)
    - Ecology Evolutionary Biology Fall 2004 Grades, 2004-2005 (Box 16, Folder 69)
    - Ecology Evolutionary Biology Spring 2005 Grades, 2004-2005 (Box 16, Folder 70)
    - Economics Fall 2004 Grades, 2004-2005 (Box 16, Folder 71)
    - Economics Spring 2005 Grades, 2004-2005 (Box 16, Folder 72)
    - Engineering Applied Science Fall 2004 Grades, 2004-2005 (Box 16, Folder 73)
    - Engineering Applied Science Spring 2005 Grades, 2004-2005 (Box 16, Folder 74)
    - English Fall 2004 Grades, 2004-2005 (Box 16, Folder 75)
    - English Spring 2005 Grades, 2004-2005 (Box 16, Folder 76)
    - Epidemiology Public Health Fall 2004 Grades, 2004-2005 (Box 16, Folder 77)
    - Epidemiology Public Health Spring 2005 Grades, 2004-2005 (Box 16, Folder 78)